you know I really I I hate to waste your
time but I'm really not looking to do
more advertising right now mhm okay yeah
I'm so sorry yeah no no worries I hear
that okay hear that gives me a certain
amount of relief thank you how you
feeling I'm in The Sweet Spot not too
drunk not too sober me too baby let's go
in for the kill you got it baby Jack
you're known all over town as the guy
with a dick in his
mouth
well it's not just sticks no it's not
it's not I've seen boobs yes seen poop I
have too I've seen a butt pooping boobs
yep seen Andre the Giant I've seen that
don't get it but I've seen it and let's
not forget about the the speech bubbles
you I'm hungry for turds that's right by
my church I'm thirsty for dongs feed me
wieners do you think it's just one
guy
no
Jack but we at cramblin duvet can put an
end to all that nonsense by rebranding
you in a television
commercial to be honest the Billboards
don't really bother me okay I actually I
I I think they're kind of funny you know
what I mean young man I know what you're
doing you're busted yeah that's great
you're using forc perspective to make it
look like I'm fting that bread stick
grow up grow up oh and there we go
dinner roll balls dinner roll balls
really original you know what I am tired
of
this sign me up let's do this all right
oh man okay champagne of beer you've
already had five drinks each je bring it
what's your problem man I am really
excited right now this this feels good
okay going to be great
Jack next time when they
ask